<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Harry Stamatoukos</title><link>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/</link><description>Recent content on Harry Stamatoukos</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data Scientist across domains</title><link>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2023_present_data_scientist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2023_present_data_scientist/</guid><description>As a data scientist I have been working in the areas of algorithmic pricing, forecasting and Natural Language Processing. Specifically, I developed a model (XGboost) that predicted which user should get a discount. This model was deployed with controled experiments (with VertexAI) and results in a 5% uplift in revenue. In Forecasting, I developed a model to forecast active riders, quarterly and yearly. This model was developed in python and achieved an accuracy of ~2-5%.</description></item><item><title>Senior Data Analyst and Data Lead</title><link>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2022_data_analyst_lead/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2022_data_analyst_lead/</guid><description>After teaching I was eager to get back in to game and develop some technology on my own. Voi, is one of the best and more complex data sets I have ever worked with. I was the first data hire of the rider domain. As a senior data analyst I took over the data ingestion (airflow &amp;amp; python), the data modelling (dbt) , builiding dahsboards (Tableau) and geospatial analytics (Unfolded &amp;amp; Python) to drive the improvement of our core rider experience.</description></item><item><title>Data Science Coach</title><link>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2020_data_science_coach/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2020_data_science_coach/</guid><description>At Multiverse I was delivering lectures in Data Science and 1to1 coaching to 50 people. I delivered lectures in Statistics, Python, Machine Learning and across the board data science. Teaching is a very efficient way of learning fundamental topics very well. Only when you have to explain something do you actually realise that you don&amp;rsquo;t understand every angle of the concept.</description></item><item><title>Strategy and Data Analyst</title><link>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2016_data_analyst_colt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2016_data_analyst_colt/</guid><description>At Colt I got my first ever job, where I was assigned the title of excel wizard. Primarily because I was good at goodling. As my first big achievement I developed a way for external customer reports to be created automatically with excel whereas before 40 service managers would create them manually taking more than a week for each service manager. This saved the company almost 50% of the time of each service manager and left them more time to take more customers on.</description></item></channel></rss>