<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Harry Stamatoukos</title><link>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/</link><description>Recent content on Harry Stamatoukos</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data Scientist across domains</title><link>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2023_present_data_scientist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2023_present_data_scientist/</guid><description>As a data scientist, my work has been focused in 3 main areas:
Algorithmic Pricing Forecasting Natural Language Processing Specifically,
On Algorithmic Pricing: I developed a model (XGboost) that decided which users should get a discount to optimize revenue. This model was deployed (VertexAI) via controled experiments and resulted in 3% increase in revenue per user. On Forecasting: I developed a model (Hierarchichal Forecasting) to forecast Active Riders, quarterly and yearly.</description></item><item><title>Senior Data Analyst and Data Lead</title><link>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2022_data_analyst_lead/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2022_data_analyst_lead/</guid><description>In late 2021 I moved to Stockholm from London and started as a Senior Data Analyst before I became the team lead of 4. Voi, is one of the best and more complex data sets I have ever worked with, given the complexity of the micromobility industry. I was the first data hire of the rider domain. As a senior data analyst I took over the data ingestion airflow &amp;amp; python, the data modelling dbt , builiding dahsboards Tableau and geospatial analytics Unfolded &amp;amp; Python to drive the improvement of our core rider experience.</description></item><item><title>Data Science Coach</title><link>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2020_data_science_coach/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2020_data_science_coach/</guid><description>At Multiverse I was delivering lectures in Data Science and 1-to-1 coaching to 50 students. I delivered lectures in Statistics, Python, Machine Learning and general Data Science topics. Teaching is a very efficient way of learning fundamental topics very well, only when one has to explain something does one actually realises that one does not understand every layer of a concept. Over the course of 2 year, I delivered almost 30 lectures and 1200 1-to-1 coaching sessions.</description></item><item><title>Strategy and Data Analyst</title><link>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2016_data_analyst_colt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.harrystamatoukos.com/experiences/_2016_data_analyst_colt/</guid><description>At Colt I got my first job, where I was titled the &amp;ldquo;excel wizard&amp;rdquo;, primarily because I was good at googling. My first big achievement was an excell reporting automation, like a primitive BI, improving the way 40 service managers created reports - from spending a week to barely a few minutes. This enabled the company to increase the number of customers that coulde be service managed, increasing revenue by offering service management to more customers.</description></item></channel></rss>